这渺小的镇
My little home
我渺小的家
This little town
不缺我一人
They don't need me
这简单的笑
My simple life
我简单的命
This simple grin
我已不信任
They betray me
你眼里的谎
Their lying eyes
虚假的笑容
My cracking shell
心上的刀痕
Their phony smiles
脸上的泪痕
My low morale
感情间的砲火
我抵抗已尽了全力
The emotional warfare
has got the best of me
只要少了我
就不会有纠纷
When you're without me
it'll be easy to share
如果需要我
就假装我在那儿
And if you need me
you can pretend I'm there
你看不到我
再也不用见到面
You'll never see me
we'll never meet again
就算少了我
你还有其他朋友
'Cause even without me,
you have your other friends
我总好奇
I wonder how
他们会怎么想
they'd think of me
如果我就此离去
if I left them
他们哪会在乎
They wouldn't mind
他们哪会介意
they wouldn't care
我也没给他们机会
I wouldn't let them
没有歌谣
No serenade
没有音乐
no lullaby
没有故事
no metaphor
能让我回头
can change my mind
毕竟遥远的那端
不过是我的「很久很久以前」
'Cause somewhere out there
is my "Once upon a time"
只要少了我
就不会有纠纷
When you're without me
it'll be easy to share
如果需要我
就假装我在那儿
And if you need me
you can pretend I'm there
你看不到我
再也不用见到面
You'll never see me
we'll never meet again
就算少了我
你还有其他朋友
'Cause even without me,
you have your other friends
只要少了我...
When you're without me...
如果需要我...
And if you need me...
你看不到我...
You'll never see me...
就算少了我...
'Cause even without me...